Kai Coleridge

Software Engineering Student

Email: kai@coleridge.me Phone: 07868 960269 Website: coleridge.me Github: github.com/kaicoleridge

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a passionate person when It comes to mobile application development. I have been developing and learning mobile application development for a while. All my experience within mobile application development is mostly in iOS Development and have built some applications to show the dedication I have to this topic.

EDUCATION

Aberystwyth University, Wales, UK — BEng in Software Engineering

SEPT 2020 - JUN 2024

I'm currently studying for a Bachelors in Software Engineering. I've completed my first year of study and currently on track to achieving a 2:1. The main modules I studied which are relevant for the job requirements are the following below:

- Programming using an OOP language
- Problems and Solutions
- Information Security

Exeter College, Exeter, UK— Level 3 Extended Diploma in Information Technology (D*D*D)

SEPT 2017 - JUL 2020

Teign School, Newton Abbot, UK — Secondary Education

SEPT 2012 - JUN 2017

English Language - 5

English Literature - 4

Maths - 4

WORK EXPERIENCE

The Cosy Club, Exeter, UK— Kitchen Assistant

SEPT 2017 - JUL 2020

- Cleaning Dishes and keeping up with hygiene basic standards
- Preparing desserts and cooking side tapas dishes and preparation of food

Zita's Bar & Grill Restaurant, Exeter, UK— Waiter

SEPT 2017 - JUL 2020

KEY SKILLS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- Self Starter Building applications and having a portfolio website demonstrates myself being a self starter, and building iOS applications. I find a sense of accomplishment from the entirety of agile development from planning & designing to a functioning end product.
- Team Player Demonstrated working in a team on numerous occasions. I demonstrated being a team player participating in Ten Tors a weekend exhibition navigating across Dartmoor for 2 days with a team of 6 people. We conducted many weeks of training together in order to complete the exhibition successfully. I've also been a member of the school band as a guitarist. Myself and the rest of the band conducted two months of rehearsals towards our final mark.
- Effective Communicator I can be an effective communicator when working with other peers. Communicate clearly to give instructions or explain certain aspects in order for someone to understand me clearly.
- Experience using Xcode and Swift/SwiftUI
- Using REST API's within Swift e.g. using OpenWeather API to retrieve weather data dependent on user location.

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Mountain Biking
- VR Gaming
- Robotics / Drones
- Travelling

- iOS Development
- Web Development
- Videography
- Photography

REFEREES

Available upon request.